<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Artur Iablokov</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Artur Iablokov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a software developer with 8 years of experience in payment services and energy monitoring systems. My curiosity and passion for information technologies drives me to experiment and apply my knowledge out of working hours. I look forward to continued involvement in projects with ambitions, wide tech stacks, and a friendly team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career</title>
      <link>/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/career/</guid>
      <description>DPS - IT for Finance, Retail &amp;amp; Public Sector Software Developer 2018 - present, Hamburg, Germany
Development of European wide leading system in the area of payment transactions
&amp;gt;100 Mio. transactions 24/7 High Load Backend &amp;gt;25 big clients (banks)
Project topics: Domestic and foreign payment transactions, Instant Payments, Clearing &amp;amp; Settlement, Backoffice, SWIFT, SEPA, MX-Migration, Reporting, etc.
Responsibilities:
Customer-oriented backend development under time pressure Responsive and targeted problem solving Analysis, consulting, review, and solution of conceptual design problems Support of the test team Development, refactoring, maintenance, optimization under existing legacy structures Effort estimation of topics and projects Dev topic examples:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/edu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/edu/</guid>
      <description>University I graduated from the University of Applied Science Hamburg with a bachelor degree in computer science in 2019. I consider myself lucky to join Prof. Becke’s group of students who specialized in distributed systems. Under Professor Becke guidance, I wrote my graduate thesis on “Analysis of a blockchain-based IoT infrastructure with Ethereum and Swarm”.
Herzlichen Glückwunsch an Artur I. für seine erfolgreiche Verteidigung. Seine BA Arbeit im Kontext von #Blockchains hat uns in unserer Arbeit weitergebracht.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects and hackathons i have participated in.
Mobility Hackathon 2018 My most recent hackathon. I participated with the team of professional and experienced developers to present an app for planning guided tours in Hamburg using public transportation. Unfortunately, the repository is private but you can check project presentation and video below.
presentation
Design the Smart Mobility – ITS Hackathon Hamburg The following hackathon was organized by Deutsche Bahn (the national railway company of Germany).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies</title>
      <link>/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>Due to changing weather conditions in Hamburg, I enjoy traveling. I am keen on water sports, historical books, and podcasts. In my free time I enjoy going to music concerts and football matches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/pexon/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pexon/about/</guid>
      <description>Specially prepared for Pexon Consulting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/pexon/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pexon/projects/</guid>
      <description>Specially prepared for Pexon Consulting</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
